Hi, I'm Joe Cuenco with Family Resources.
We're talking today about how to improve our marriage relationships, specifically, how do we pamper our wife?
This may be the most important thing that we do in our marriage.
So listen carefully as we talk about how do we pamper our wife.
This is really going to be specific to your wife's personality.
Each woman has things that are very important to her, and there are things that she doesn't like as well.
So it's very important that we pay attention to these things.
But before we pay attention to them, we first have to understand and know what they are.
Have a dialog with your wife.
Ask her what it is that makes her feel special.
Ask her what it is that makes her feel like the most important person in the world.
You need to dote on your wife, you need to pamper her.
Do these things to make her feel special.
Of course, the foundation fundamentals have to be there.
Love, trust, respect, friendship, communication.
Those are huge, but building upon those are ways that you can actually make your wife feel very special.
Buying here chocolates, buying her flowers.
When was the last time you rubbed her back, or gave her a foot massage.
Or actually, perhaps, rubbed her back in the jacuzzi, doing something to really make her feel special.
How are you with her...her family members?
You know, this is important to mention, being able to get along with the family, her mother.
You want to eliminate those things as far as any...any stress in the relationship.
And also, make sure that she has the physical attention that she needs. Are you holding her hand? Are you....are you putting you arm around her?
Are you opening up the door for her when you go out on dates?
And also on the...one the intimacy side, are you giving her more than you expect?
And is she getting less than you want to give perhaps?
So, it needs to have a happy medium.
So, have a dialog there.
Be prepared to give, and ultimately you'll receive.
Doctor John Gray of the Venus and Mars book series, has a lot of good advice here.
There's other things that you can do.
Attend workshops.
But it may be as simple as sitting down and watching TV with her, a TV program.
And I would suggest doing that, except don't watch Desperate Housewives.
So, make sure that you pay attention to your wife, make her feel special.
And that's how you pamper your wife.
I'm Joe Cuenco, with Family Resources, Relationships for Life.